<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Yawhe Shamma TV </string>
    <string name="addUnit">ca-app-pub-7233052509464359/5936673806</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="contactus1"><b> GRDP InfoTech, Pune </b></string>
    <string name="contactus2">E-3,Jhandewala Estate,Rani Jhansi Marg,New Delhi-110055,
    Phone:23529557,41398888
    Email:delpress@bol.net.in</string>
    <string name="contactus3">
        M-12,Connaught Circus,
        New Delhi-110001
        Phone 23416313</string>


    <string name="welcommsg">Welcome to \n Yawhe Shamma Evangelical Church </string>
    <string name="tagline">
        <b>“Send us around the world with the news of your saving power and your eternal plan for all mankind”</b> (Psalms 67:2)

\n\nPastor Narendra Gaikwad  is the founder and Senior Pastor of Yawhe Shamma Evanglical Church in Pune.  In response to the call of God he dedicated his life to Christ more than 20 years ago and a vision was delivered to him to start the ministry and establish Churches.

\n\nPastor Gaikwad is mightily used by God in healing, deliverance and teaching ministry. Making his life count with God by making an impact with the Gospel and being committed to soul winning he has worked tirelessly over the years to establish 3 Churches around Pune and has been instrumental in equipping God’s people with the Word of God.

    </string>
    <string name="marathitag">याव्हे शामा इव्हेन्जीकल चर्च मध्ये तुमचे स्वागत आहे.</string>


    <string name="abouttext"> Yave Shama Evangelical Church is a multi-lingual full-gospel Assembly of God (AG) Church in Pune City.
        Our Vision and Mission is to bring the unreached to Jesus Christ through evangelism, lead them to worship the Almighty God, make them true disciples of Christ with due fellowship with the body of Christ, and cater to the needs of the society through humanitarian services.

View Worship Schedule


    </string>
    <string name="Link_Request">If you don\'t have E-mail account <u> Click Here </u> </string>

    <string name="swap"> --------- swap --------- </string>


    <string name="vision">

    The Christian Reformed Church is a diverse family of healthy congregations, assemblies, and ministries expressing the good news of God’s kingdom that transforms lives and communities worldwide.
</string>

    <string name="mision">

    \nAs people called by God,

    \n\n We gather to praise God, listen to him, and respond.
      \n\n We nurture each other in faith and obedience to Christ.
      \n\n We love and care for one another as God's people.
      \n\n We commit ourselves to serve and to tell others about Jesus.
      \n\n We pursue God's justice and peace in every area of life.

</string>


    <string name="pastormsg"> Rev. Narendra V. Gaikwad has been the pastor of Pune Yave Shama Evangelical Church ever since its genesis in 1993.

\n\n I was born in a very orthodox Christian family. My father was a central government employee with a transferable job. Being born in such a background, money and status were always with us. There was no need to search for God. Life continued and I started growing in this family. Many times we rejected God’s people and spoke against them, belittling them.

\n\n In the year 1985 we went to Calcutta and were part of the Buntain Memorial Assemblies of God Church. In May 1987, I attended a VBS in the same church where on the final day I accepted Jesus Christ as my personal saviour. In June 1987 I obeyed the Lord in water baptism and God filled me with his Holy Spirit with the evidence of talking in tongues, vision, and prophesy and I started rooting myself in Christ.

\n\n In September 2000 I got married to Glory Shine, and life continued the same. In the year 2003 we moved to HBR Layout i.e., Hennur Depot, Bangalore and started a small prayer with just my wife and my son, Sam 7 months of age. God gave us an increase. In 2004 October we started as a morning service in English with just 20 people and named the church City Harvest AG Church.

\n\n Over the years God has blessed and increased our attendance and membership and now we have about 700 people worshipping God on all Sundays. We have services in 6 different languages and baptisms on a monthly basis.

\n\n Now the ministry is still going on with God leading us day-by-day with signs, wonders and miracles.

\n\n Pastor Shine is married to Glory Shine and is the proud father of two children, Son Samuel P. Shine and daughter Grace Ann Shine.

\n\n Rev. Narendra V. Gaikwad
\nFounder and Senior Pastor</string>


    <string name="staff"> Ministerial Staff </string>
    <string name="title_activity_testimonial">Testimonial</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="send_request_via_whatapp">Send Request Via WhatApp</string>


    <string name="note"><i> Click Following any Button To Pay now.</i></string>
    <string name="sharelink">To Download Yawhe Shamma TV Android application click on following link.   \\n\\n     https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=grdpinfotech.ganeshsatkar.yavechurch</string>


</resources>
